Well, first of all, the black people in Chicago are thrilled that we're getting the illegal aliens out of their communities who are stealing their housing, jobs, and resources.
You've seen the video of the town halls during the Biden administration where black citizens who are natives of Chicago were begging to have the illegals taken out of their country.
What they've done is they've created a system of law in Chicago, in Illinois, where illegal aliens have far more rights than American citizens.
If an American citizen, for example, commits a crime of sexual predation against a child, they'll cooperate with the FBI.
If an illegal alien commits a crime of sexual predation against a child, that illegal alien will be shielded in an ICE no-go zone.
I ask you the question, what is the right term to describe a local official declaring a no-go zone for ICE?
Would you tolerate it for FBI, ATF, DEA?
No, you would not.
But there is an effort to delegitimize the core function of the federal government of enforcing our immigration laws and our sovereignty.
It is domestic terrorism.
It is insurrection.
And no amount of insane, hyperventilating lies from Pritzker or Johnson or any other Democratic official will change our minds on that.
ICE officers should not have to live in fear and violence to do their jobs.
Period.
So on the substance of the question, is it the case that as Pritzker frames it, you are profiling brown people,
that this immigration crackdown is designed to go after people of color?